<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kean Rawr</title>
    <link>https://keanrawr.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kean Rawr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://keanrawr.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Scrape emojis for slack</title>
      <link>https://keanrawr.github.io/p/scrape-emojis-for-slack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keanrawr.github.io/p/scrape-emojis-for-slack/</guid>
      <description>Why do this? One of the most common pieces of advice that data science newbies get is to learn web scraping, this is usually acompanied by an argument like: &amp;ldquo;WS is a really important skill for data science, since being able to scrape your own dataset from the web comes in handy&amp;rdquo;.
As a person who dives head first into anything that&amp;rsquo;s deemed &amp;ldquo;highly valuable&amp;rdquo; I went head first into learning web scraping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting mlflow on Raspberry Pi Behind nginx</title>
      <link>https://keanrawr.github.io/p/hosting-mlflow-on-raspberry-pi-behind-nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keanrawr.github.io/p/hosting-mlflow-on-raspberry-pi-behind-nginx/</guid>
      <description>Why you need to track experiments As data scientists or Machine Learning engineers one of the most overlook things is &amp;ldquo;model lineage&amp;rdquo;, that is, being able to track the data and hyper parameters used to produce a model. This helps ensure reproducibility, which is really important for a number of reasons.
mlflow isn&amp;rsquo;t the only tool that helps us track experiments, but is the one I like the most, other tools for experiment tracking are: comet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://keanrawr.github.io/p/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keanrawr.github.io/p/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
This is the first official post on my new blog! In this blog I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about data projects that I develop on my free time, and some of the techniques that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned over my professional career.
A little about me: I&amp;rsquo;m a data scientist that loves to write code, I love writing in R but focus mainly on python for my professional work. I love playing basketball, not actually a real hard-core NBA fan, but I might start getting more interested in the league to do some fantasy league analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
